[{"category":"Neo Technology","question":"Who has an intimate strategic partnership with a journalist?","answer":"Emil Eifrem"},
{"category":"Neo Technology","question":"Who sells free software?","answer":"Charlie Fischer"},
{"category":"Neo Technology","question":"Who wrote software for the Steal Fighter?","answer":"Adam Frankl"},
{"category":"Neo Technology","question":"Who sails in the lovely blue waters of the Aegean sea?","answer":"Chris Gioran"},
{"category":"Neo Technology","question":"Who is the refridgertor guy?","answer":"Bjorn Granvik"},
{"category":"Neo Technology","question":"Who is the company's master mixologist?","answer":"Jacob Hansson"},
{"category":"Neo Technology","question":"Who owns their own coffeeshop co-working space?","answer":"Michael Hunger"},
{"category":"Neo Technology","question":null,"answer":"Tobias Ivarsson"},
{"category":"Neo Technology","question":"Who can give you advice about plastic surgery?","answer":"Michaela Johansson"},
{"category":"Neo Technology","question":"How big is who's potato?","answer":"Alistair Jones"},
{"category":"Neo Technology","question":"Who is here only metaphorically?","answer":"Andreas Kollegger"},
{"category":"Neo Technology","question":"Who dreams of restoring a house in the Italian countryside?","answer":"Edward Lombardo"},
{"category":"Neo Technology","question":"Who recently delivered their own child?","answer":"David Montag"},
{"category":"Neo Technology","question":"Who is plays jazz guitar to relax?","answer":"Anders Nawroth"},
{"category":"Neo Technology","question":"Who is Node id 0?","answer":"Peter Neubauer"},
{"category":"Neo Technology","question":null,"answer":"Lars Nordwall"},
{"category":"Neo Technology","question":null,"answer":"Rickard Oberg"},
{"category":"Neo Technology","question":null,"answer":"Mattias Persson"},
{"category":"Neo Technology","question":"Who is a scholar of Elizabethan literature?","answer":"Ian Robinson"},
{"category":"Neo Technology","question":"Who founded the Barcelona branch of the Surfrider Foundation?","answer":"Allison Sparrow"},
{"category":"Neo Technology","question":null,"answer":"Johan Svensson"},
{"category":"Neo Technology","question":"Who will kick your ass if you don't behave?","answer":"Andres Taylor"},
{"category":"Neo Technology","question":null,"answer":"Jim Webber"},
{}]